CURRICULUM VITAE

Adriana Zonari Lindblad

I am a driven, creative, social, team worker and selfgoing professional. Thanks to many years of selfemployment and small business, I am used to handling multiple parallel tasks and drive them to completion.



From my time as a professional rider and trainer, as well as the years in the food industry I bring with me above all, social skills, structure, leadership, perfectionism and the ability to get jobs done in time.

The passion for business combined with the fast development of the digital world has inspired me to reach new goals and diving in the digital universe for an upgrade was an obvious choice. I focus my expertise in business analysis and digital communication, but I am also a skilled web developer and am comfortable working in an agile environment.

I am a fast learner, not afraid of changes and am driven by challenges. Structure is prioritized at work and motivation is on top when goals are set.

WORK EXPERIENCE

06/2018-11/2018

IKEA GROUP, MALMÖ/HELSINBORG
Internship at IKEA Store App team. Focused on business analysis and communication (both intern and extern), ASO, SEO of the app. I was also responsible for the creation and distribution of training material to customers support and web team in all markets. We worked with Agile principles which suits me well since it is necessary to be proactive and team worker.

02/2015- 10/2018

Ängavallen, Vellinge Head Dairyman:

Responsible for the whole dairy production, such as production planning, cheesemaking, fermented products, HACCP and daily routines, storage and development of new products. Helping with the company's webshop, social media and developing of the home page was also part of my job.

06 /2013 -10/2015

Brunslövs Mejeri

My own dairy where I basically made everything from scratch. From the idea, logo, marketing, sales, designing labels and packaging, homepage, social medias, until the products were in the market. I had daily contact with the production and development of new products, as well as prospection of new customers and market opportunities.

2000 - 2012

Zonari Dressage

My own company where I trained horses and riders at competition level both in Brazil and Sweden, where I moved to in 2003. Among them, I was the dressage trainer for the eventing Brazilian team that took a gold medal in the South American Championships, in 2002. I also competed at a high level both around the country and internationally.

Selling and export of sporthorses around the world were a big part of my business. I prospected customers and matched horses. I also supported the customer during the whole process. From a telephone call in the beginning, until their visit to try the horse in Europe, negotiation buyer/seller, transport to their new home and after sales support, training them regularly on place.

1999

Roche Pharmaceuticals Brasil Trainee at their advertising trainee program

Seven Advertising Agency 1997-1998

Account Manager

EDUCATION

2017 - Dec 2018 Malmös Yrkeshögskolan

Mobil Handel - Frontend Developing, Digital

Marketing, e-commerce

2013 Folkuniversitet Yrkeshögskola

Artisanal Food Production, Entrepreneurship,

Marketing

1996 - 2001 Universidade Paulista

Marketing and Advertising

1993 Waterstock House Training Center, Oxford,

England

Training horse riding at competition level and

studying english.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Portuguese (mother tongue), English (fluent), Swedish (fluent), Spanish (basics), French (basics)

IT SKILLS

Office Package

Adobe Package

Html, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, Wordpress and

Woocommerce

ASO, SEO, SEM, SMO

Google Analytics - Advanced certification by Google

Project Management with Agile principles